APURVA A BHOSALE

APURVA. A. BHOSALE

Add:103/E2/PHASE-6/BRAHMAND CHS/GB ROAD/THANE (W) MAHARASHTRA/ INDIA

Email: apu22feb90@gmail.com

Ph: +91 8600892230/ +974 70326702

Nationality: - Indian

Passport Number: - P 4883066

Gender: - Female Marital status: - Married Date of Birth: 14 AUG 1989 Languages: English, Hindi, Marathi Current Work Location: - DOHA, QATAR

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

An achievement oriented Engineer with an overseas experience in ERP implementation, IT operations and human capital management. Backed by an eclectic experience in the technical industry with exposure over software development and database management systems. Excellent communication and presentation skills which have always rendered problem solving ability.

Backed by above <u>5 years' experience</u> in the Software/IT industry.

SKILLS

- IT operations Management
- HC Management
- Project Coordination
- Document Control
- Database management
- Software Implementation
- Techno-Functional Trainings
- Software Development
- Software Support
- API (Application Programming Interface) Integration
- C.±
- SQL Server 2005, 2008r2
- Asp.Net
- Ado.Net

APURVA. A. BHOSALE

WORK EXPERIENCE

PROJECT ANALYST | VISTAS GLOBAL | DOHA, QATAR

NOV 2017 TO PRESENT

Vistas Global is a multifaceted company with headquarters in **Qatar** that provides solutions and services in technology and operations management.

CLIENTS

- COMMERCIAL BANK QATAR (CBQ)
- QATAR FOUNDATION
- PRIMARY HEALTH CARE CORPORATION (PHCC)
- VODAFONE QATAR
- BEIN SPORTS

MAJOR RESPONSIBILITIES

- Analyze project resourcing requirements from Key Clients.
- Engage in project kick off meetings, understanding client's project based requirements and preparing execution plan.
- Review candidate profiles and prioritize on the basis of their compatibility with the technical requirement of the project.
- Conduct initial interviews with the candidates.
- Negotiate deliverables, schedules and commercial aspects.
- Manage resources onboard with all the key accounts.
- Responsible for updating and maintaining employee database in ERP system.

SOFTWARE SUPPORT ENGINEER | ANVIN QATAR WLL | DOHA, QATAR

AUG 2017 TO NOV 2017

Anvin Technologies Incorporation is promoted by a team of technical and management professionals with over 25 years of experience in providing quality end to end solutions in ERP, CRM, application development, mobile and firmware applications, System integration ,IT infrastructure, access control , RFID & Biometric systems, and Remote Infrastructure Management.

CLIENTS

VISTAS GOBAL, DOHA, QATAR

MAJOR RESPONSIBILITIES

- To incorporate company's data into ERP modules.
- To conduct regular presentations and trainings on software handling & troubleshooting.
- To work with client staff in order for them to get used to the user interface.
- To follow up and expedite the data integration process among different departments of

the client organization.

- To get constant feedback from users for necessary changes or need for additional features.
- To negotiate deliverables, schedules and costing for additional services.
- To coordinate with internal developer team and facilitate client needs.
- To monitor constant progress and expedite/complete the project in the given time period. Justify the client & management in case of extensions required due to additional services. In any case, try to expedite and deliver the promises.
- To update/report management on timely basis regarding project progress.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | INFINIA SOLUTIONS & SERVICES | MUMBAI, INDIA JAN 2015 TO MAY 2016

PROJECT 1: "MASTERPASS" (CHECKOUT PRODUCT SOFTWARE)

CLIENT: AXIS BANK.

Project details: With Master pass, we have developed a global offering for merchants and financial institutions. Master pass makes it easier for customers to make online purchase in stores through integrated acceptance.

PROJECT 2: "VIATOR" (PRODUCT WITH MULTIPLE TOUR GRADES) CLIENT: VIATOR INTERNATIONAL.

Project details: VIATOR is a tour and travelling site developed as a global offering for merchants. Our software makes it easier for customers to book a product (Tour) along with multiple Tour-grades (Extra Facilities) online through an integrated solution. Integration done with the help <u>WCF services</u>. Project developed on <u>.Net Framework 4th version</u>.

SKILLS: Asp.net 4.5 and 1.1, SQL server 2008R2, Reporting Services and, Ajax calls and ERP validations.

MAJOR RESPONSIBILITIES:

- Coordinate with the users and the team whenever required, issue management and coordination with the team related to bug fixes.
- Analyzing client requirements.
- Testing and maintain the database.
- Finding stored procedures, queries in large database using SQL server profiler and fixing the errors, finding errors in reports.
- Generate DDL and DML statements.
- Creation of client, Adding of Service References, integrating Endpoints.
- Integrating API's (Application Programming Interface).
- Testing API Request, Response methods, Creation of Interface, Adding Implementer.
- Integration of Payment Gateway for booking Process in Viator.

APURVA. A. BHOSALE

- Creation of ASPX pages using Asp.net (Shipping and billing address).
- Applying design to pages, CSS, checking Request and response on server.
- Creation of Templates, or Adding Validations, Creation of AJAX calls.
- Deployment and pointing of complete project on server with help of IIS manager, which includes Creation of website, adding a virtual directory, setting application pool, Creating SQL server instance. Deployment of Reports on Server.

T-SQL DEVELOPER | AGILE FINANCIAL TECHNOLOGIES | MUMBAI, INDIA NOV 2013 TO JAN 2015

PROJECT NAME: "MINTMONEY"

Project details: "MINTMONEY" is an end to end solution for a bank (client) to process and track its offered Loans. It allows the bank to configure varied combinations of settings, based on the business need. It provides a dashboard to all levels of the vertical to monitor the business and assist in the day to day operations.

MAJOR RESPONSIBILITIES:

- Configure the production server.
- Give training to the customer
- Configure the Product; develop pages according to the project need.
- Integration of a request and response.
- Customization according to the business requirement.
- Creating custom report and provide ADHOC summary from the production environment.

ACADEMIC PROJECT

WIRELESS ROBOT TO DETECT HARMFUL GASES IN MINES

The application is a milestone achievement in the core mining industry. India presently needs automated robotic systems in most of the industrial applications in order to achieve technological and economical excellence.

PROGRAMMING: 8051 MICROCONTROLLER

TRAININGS & CERTIFICATIONS

 DIPLOMA IN .NET (NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (NIIT)), INDIA.

APURVA. A. BHOSALE

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING (B.E- ELECTRONICS)

UNIVERSITY: PUNE (INDIA)

GRADE: FIRST CLASS (AGG: 66%, EQUI CGPA-3.2/4)

12TH GRADE (SCIENCE)

BOARD: HSC (INDIA)

GRADE: FIRST CLASS (AGG: 60%)

10TH GRADE

BOARD: SSC (INDIA)

GRADE: FIRST CLASS (AGG: 72%)

HOBBIES

- Painting
- Music & Dance
- Event Management

DECLARATION: I, Apurva Abhijit Bhosale, hereby declare that all the details furnished are true to my knowledge.

APURVA ABHIJIT BHOSALE

DATE: TIME: